Register of the S. I. Hayakawa papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington Office, Administrative/Legislative Files (Boxes 1-265)
  - Photographs (Box 236)
    - 6/27/80
      - Dr. Kim, Dr. Backer
      - Intern Melanie Hartounian
      - Sharon Bukowski
    - Suzanne and Tim Kelly, 7/1/80
    - 7/2/80
      - Lawrence Spector of Big Sur
      - Youth Science Camp Winners
    - Herman Miller, oldest vet of Spanish American War, 7/21/80
    - 7/22/80
      - Intern Liz Holmes
      - The Kipps
      - CA Assn. Winegrape Growers
      - Jim Brulte
    - 7/24/80
      - Washington Workshop
      - Boys Nation delegates
      - Intern Kevin Early
    - Pam Carson, 7/27/80
    - George Bush, 7/29/80
    - 8/1/80
      - SIH in baseball outfit
      - Gene Prat, Janice Barbieri, Laurie Baker
    - 8/5/80
      - Indian Youth
      - Intern Ron Jacob
    - 8/19/80
      - The Kwongs
      - The Effrons
      - Chinese Welfare Council
    - 8/22/80
      - Intern Bill Williams
      - Senate pages
      - Richard Sandifer, staff
      - Brian Maxwel, staff
      - Various Senate pages
      - Mike Gervais
    - Jill Lindstrom, 8/26/80
    - SIH and Cranston, 8/27/80
    - Mike Montgomery, 8/80
    - Charles Julian, 9/4/80
    - Richard Hirschfeld and Dr. Backer, 9/5/80
    - 9/8/80
      - Mayor Larry Bagley of Oceanside
      - Jerry Partian
      - Rod Holmgren
      - John Briscoe and Nicholas Gismond
    - Ernest Nankos, 9/9/80
    - 9/15/80
      - Intern Charles Butt
      - Intern Nancy Carson
      - Intern Cari Cooper
      - Intern Brian Colburn
      - Anne Moore, staff
      - Pat Okura
      - Intern Matt Stankey
      - Jerry Jackson of GEICO
      - Kenneth Harrel and family
      - Ken Zuck
    - 9/17/80
      - Kitchenaires from Eureka
      - Wilson Johnson of NFIB
    - 9/18/80
      - Perry Galloway
      - Jon Mong
      - Vicki Bie
    - 9/19/80
      - Thelma Osborn
      - Telephone Pioneers of America
      - Mrs. John Sandoval and Mrs. Harry Collins
    - 9/24/80
      - Lee Tarbet, Intern
      - L.A. City College Robert Farrell
      - Senator Montoya
      - David and Carol Hwang
    - Black Business Assn. of L.A., 9/29/80
    - National Associated Businessmen, Inc., 10/1/80 (Box 243)
    - Rols Kravlik family, 10/2/80
    - Page Sam Fairley, 11/12/80
    - Ray Bennett, VP 20th Century Fox, 11/13/80
    - 11/14/80
      - Jim Josoff and Big Sur Group
      - CA County Supervisors
      - Toastmasters International
    - 11/18/80
      - Victor Levy, President FTD
      - Wally Amos, "Famous Amos"
    - Republican Caucus, 12/2/80
    - 12/4/80
      - Peggy Haberstroh and Don Maag, Jr. of Norris Industries
      - Andy Walquist, Senator Warner's AA
      - Lori Sonken, Cheryl Orpen
    - Cheryl Orpen and parents, 12/16/80
    - Republican Caucus, 12/80
    - 1/81
      - Hirschhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden (SIH & Warren)
      - Co-op Bank of S.F.
    - Rev. Ray Mossholder, 1/19/81
    - 1/23/81
      - Staff interns
      - Intern Amy Burland
      - Keith Coplen, staff, and Scott Adair, intern
      - Inter Christine Ingate
    - 1/26/81
      - Howard Sitton of Big Sur
      - Mary Carpenter of Encino
    - 1/27/81
      - St. Mary's College students
      - Bill Anton
    - Tado Ishikawa of Asia Foundation, 1/29/81
    - 2/3/81
      - CA School Board
      - George Nicholson, VP CBS, Miriam Burre of same
    - 2/4/81
      - Hearst delegates
      - Steve Kelmar, staff
      - Intern Susan Saransky
      - Mystery students
    - Senator Heflin, 2/19/81
    - 2/24/81
      - CA State Student Assn.
      - Frances Compton, CA Community College Trustee
    - 2/25/81
      - Intern Maria Draper
      - Intern Michelle Chauvin
      - Staff Tom Wilkinson
      - Intern Erin Riley
      - Senator Hatch page Jennens
      - Walt Furen, staff
      - Intern James Rule
      - Mary Goedde, staff
    - Former Congressman Pat Hillings, 2/26/81
    - Country Supervisors of CA, 3/9/81
    - BART officials, 3/10/81
    - SBA Michael Cardenas, 3/11/81
    - Iran rally, 3/12/81
    - Big Sur, 3/18/81
    - Takeo Foundation, 3/19/81
    - Bob Ferris, Bill Walsh, 3/20/81
    - Cherry Blossom Princess Anne Long, 3/23/81
    - 3/25/81
      - Atlantic Richfield Civic Action Program
      - Twyla Thompson, Yolo County Supervisor
    - Judge Green, 3/27/81
    - Oakland Chamber of Commerce, 3/31/81
    - Intern photos, 4/81
    - Parents Who Care, 4/1/81
    - 4/6/81
      - CA Medical Assn.
      - Giles Welsh of Malibu
    - 4/7/81
      - Kerry Wilhite, 4-H Rep.
      - Jay Van Andel, Amway Chairman
    - UPS Executives, 4/8/81
    - L.A. Area School Field Studies, 4/81
    - Interns, 5/81
    - 5/5/81 (Box 244)
      - S.D. County Officials
      - CA Building Association
    - 5/15/81
      - Woodward Kingman, Crocker Bank
      - Charles Huggins, Sees Candy
    - Senior interns, 5/20/81
    - Chancellor Helmut Schmidt, 5/27/81
    - Contract Sheet w/Senator Laxalt, 5/81
    - Tours for Teens, 6/15/81
    - 6/23/81
      - Intern Greg Houstanic
      - Frank Chuman, Patrick Olawa of L.A.
    - 6/25/81
      - Norman Livermore
      - DOD Sec. Caspar Weinberger
    - Interns, 7/81
    - 7/16/81
      - Jr. Statesmen and Santa Barbara Chamber
      - President Reagan and reception for new CA Congressmen
    - 7/22/81
      - Urban League
      - Black Mayors Director J. S. Alexander
      - South Korean Parliament tea
    - Boy Scout Jamboree Troop 722, 7/23/81
    - Boy Scouts, 7/28/81
    - 8/81
      - Eureka Rotary Club
      - Spring Dinner Dance
      - Stanley Diamond, staff
    - Lemore Naval Station, 9/11/81
    - Mayor Harold Hockett of Ridgecrest, CA, 9/16/81
    - 9/30/81
      - John Van de Water, Chairman of NLRB
      - Al Gilliland, President Gil Industries of San Jose
    - King Juan Carlos, 10/14/81
    - David McCoskey, 11/4/81
    - 11/5/81
      - James Watt, Secretary of the Interior
      - King Hussein of Jordan
    - Soule Group of Walnut Creek, 11/13/81
    - Center for Strategic Studies lunch honoring Dr. Chin, 11/18/81
    - White House Congressional Christmas Party, 12/81
    - White House Conference on Aging, 12/2/81
    - Shirley Brinker, CA Farmer, 12/8/81
    - Steering Committee, luncheon, 12/9/81
    - Congressman Jerry Lewis, 12/10/81
    - 1/82
      - Anna Chennault and Senator Hatch
      - Senator Metzenbaum
    - Hearst Youth Foundation, 2/3/82
    - David Courson, 2/8/82
    - CA County Supervisors, William Taft H.S. students, Page Marietta, Herbert Kurit of McDonald's, 2/23/82
    - Paul Vallely, 2/25/82
    - University of Wisconsin alumni, 3/82
    - CA League of Cities, 3/1/82
    - Diane May, staff, and John Nelson, intern, 3/3/82
    - 3/10/82
      - Congressman Wayne Grisham
      - Dan Roundtree, Congressman Goldwater intern
    - Sister Welding of L.A., 3/11/82
    - El Dorado H.S. students, 4/8/82
    - 4/14/82
      - Jay Noonan
      - Steve Sasholin
      - Interns
    - Francis Ravel, Mike Haynes of S.B. Ctte, 4/22/82
    - 4/23/82
      - Pages, interns
      - Richard Siegel, friend of Jeff Marston's
      - Lisa Nichols, Jim Brulte (staff)
    - Evans School students, 4/26/82
    - Fallbrook H.S., 5/3/82
    - College students, 5/5/82
    - Richard Sandifer (staff) and mom, 5/6/82
    - Senior Citizen interns, 5/20/82
    - President Lubota, 5/13/82
    - 5/24/82
      - Senator Helms/Ted Turner luncheon
      - Donald Smith, Richard Sandifer's friend
    - 6/14/82 (Box 245)
      - Margaret Pool, intern
      - Antelope Valley Board of Trade
      - Xerox Contest winners
    - National Energy Education Day recipients, 6/17/82
    - Congressman Moorehead's office interns, 6/17/82
    - Marian Hopkins and brother, 6/23/82
    - National Youth Science Camp winners, 7/21/82
    - William Way, 7/23/82
    - Interns, 7/26/82
    - South Korean Delegation, 7/27/82
    - 7/29/82
      - Boys Nation delegates
      - Korean graduate students
      - Linnea Bohn, page
    - Branan Allison, Ray Hill, Mr. & Mrs. Fairbairn, 8/3/82
    - Katy Graves, 8/4/82
    - Paul Miller, page, 8/10/82
    - Pages, interns, 8/19/82
    - Small Business hearing, 9/16/82
    - 9/17/82
      - President Marcos
      - Agriculture
      - Mystery student groups
  - Presiding hours record for SIH
  - Lobbyists seen
  - County files
    - Alameda
    - Butte
    - Contra Costa
    - El Dorado
    - Fresno
    - Humbolt
    - Imperial
    - Inyo
    - Kern
    - Kings
    - Lassen
    - Los Angeles
    - Madera
    - Marin
    - Mendocino
    - Merced (Box 246)
    - Monterey
    - Napa
    - Nevada
    - Orange
    - Palo Alto
    - Placer
    - Riverside
    - Sacramento
    - San Bernardino
    - San Diego
    - San Francisco
    - San Joaquin
    - San Jose
    - San Luis Obispo
    - San Mateo
    - Santa Ana
    - Santa Barbara
    - Santa Clara
    - Santa Cruz
    - Shasta
    - Solano
    - Sonoma
    - Stanislaus
    - Stockton
    - Sutter
    - Tulare-Visalia
    - Ventura
    - Wilmington
    - Yolo
    - Yuba
    - Non-California
  - Scheduling information and schedules, 1978-1979 (Box 247)
    - Trips, 1977-1980
      - Orient trip, 1977
      - Africa trip, 1978
      - Alaska trip, 1978
      - Interparliamentary Symposium, Tokyo, 1978
      - Russia, Brussels, Rome, 1979
      - Korea trip, 1979
      - Taiwan trip, 1980
    - Itinerary
      - 1977
      - 1978
      - 1979
      - California appointments, 1979
      - 1980
    - Invitations (Box 248)
      - Accepts, 1979
      - Accepts, 1980
      - Media invitations, 1979
      - Political invitations, 1978-1979
      - Appointments, accepts, 1982
  - Travel & Expenses/Engagements/Functions, 1979-1982
    - Expense request letters, 1979-1980
    - Republican Convention, 7/12/80
    - "Tom Brown Dinner," Pittsburgh, PA, 11/10/80
    - Travel schedule/reimbursement, October-December 1981
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Tour & Luncheon, 12/3/81
    - California Republican State Convention, Palm Springs, 10/1/81
    - Travel schedule, January 4-19, 1982
    - Pacific Union College Lecture, "Pluralism,", 1/18/82
    - Republican State Convention, Monterey; SNAK/PAC Convention, Las Vegas, 1/29-2/2/82
    - Sacramento/San Diego/Los Angeles trip, 2/11-2/21/82
    - Interview with KCET-TV, Guest Workers, 3/5/82
    - Jr. State - USC, Los Angeles/Western Regional Conference YAF, 3/6/82
    - Easter Recess, 4/2-4/12/82
    - May trips to California &, April 30th, 1982
    - National Nutritional Foods Association Convention, New Orleans, 7/24/82
    - July & August trip schedule, 1982
    - SIH address Peace Corps Convention, Washington, D.C., 9/20/82
    - Republican Fundraiser & Presentation of President Reagan's letter to Mrs. Adler, Clearwater, Florida, 9/24/82
    - September &, October 1982
    - November &, December 1982
    - SIH travel airfares, October 1981-December 1982
  - Mobile office files, December 1978-December 1981 (Box 249)
  - Travel (Box 250)
    - January-June 1978
    - July-December 1978
    - January-December 1979 (Box 251)
    - January-June 1980
    - July-December 1980
  - Office operations (Box 252-254)
    - Mass mailings, telegrams, memoranda, etc.
    - Appointment book, 1982 (Box 255)
  - Special projects
  - Special projects (Box 256-257)
  - Weekly Legislative Reports (Box 258)
    - January-August 1977
    - September-December 1977
    - February-April 1978 (Box 259)
    - May-July 1978
    - August-September 1978
  - Daily Legislative Reports, January-August 1978
  - Press columns, 1977-1982 (Box 260)
  - Press videotapes (Box 261)
  - Grace/Archival, 1978-1980 (Box 262)
  - Grace/Archival, 1978-1980 (Box 263)
  - Photographs & Plaques (Box 264)
    - Photographs
    - Assorted cartoons
    - San Diego Union cartoon, 1977 (Box 265)
    - Letter from President Reagan, 1982
    - Denver Post cartoon, 1979
    - Washington's Farewell Address
- U.S. Senate Correspondence Management System Office File (Boxes 266-310)
  - Computer Management Office (Box 266-269)
    - Microfilm tapes 1-88; Document Numbers 7046422001-8096441029
    - Microfilm tapes 89-173; Document Numbers 809643007-83105211002 (Box 270-273)
    - Microfilm tapes 174-261; Document Numbers 8310581001-9226523446 (Box 274-277)
    - Microfilm tapes 262-342; Document Numbers 92274531001-0162643111 (Box 278-281)
    - Microfilm tapes 343-433; Docuemnt Numbers 0163331001-1152453162 (Box 282-285)
    - Microfilm tapes 434-522; Document Numbers 115243162-2040663362 (Box 286-289)
    - Name Report 77 (2 tapes) (Box 290-293)
    - Name Report 78 (7 tapes)
    - Name Report 79 (10 tapes)
    - Name Report 80 (11 tapes)
    - Name Report 81 (11 tapes)
    - Name Report 82 (6 tapes)
    - Library 79 (2 tapes)
    - Library 80 (3 tapes)
  - California files
    - 1-32
    - 33-48 (Box 294-297)
  - Buck files, (18), 1979-1981
  - Tapes, constituent correspondence
    - 523-576
    - 577-604 (Box 298-301)
  - California Cases, 1977-1979
  - Profession Codes Index (Box 302)
  - Agency Codes
  - Computer Management Reference Guide
  - Memorabilia, photography, certificates, plaques (Box 303-307)
  - Administrative files, office management (Box 308)
    - COEA
      - Reimbursement 10% Account, 1981
      - Reimbursement (4 part vouchers), 1981
      - Reimbursement 10% Account, 1980
      - Reimbursement (4 part), (Feb. 27-) (Box 309)
      - Reimbursement, (Jan 28)
      - Reimbursement Part One, (Jan 1)
      - Reimbursement, 1977-1979 (Box 310)
    - Senator's travel reimbursement, 1981
    - Travel reimbursement, July 1-December 31, 1981
    - Travel reimbursement, January 1-June 30, 1981
- San Francisco and Other California District Offices File (Boxes 311-406)
  - Fresno Office (Box 311-326)
  - Orange County Office (Box 327-329)
    - Advisory Committees
      - Education
      - Agriculture
      - Budget
      - Energy
      - Child Care
      - Federal Selection
      - Health Issues
      - Welfare
      - Natural Resources
    - Reports of Sub-Committee on Energy
    - Potential Advisory Committee members
    - Legal (Box 330-331)
    - Law Enforcement
    - Industry
    - Immigration
    - International Trade Advisory Committee
    - Small Business Committee
    - Health Systems
    - Computer print-out
    - Campaign, 1976 (Box 332-334)
      - P.A.C.'s
      - Werbel invoices
      - Reider event
      - Republican Congressional boosters
      - Primary donors letter
      - RSCCC Convention
      - Dr. Richard
      - Doug Hallett
      - Dill A. Swanson
      - Murphy Fund
      - Contra Costa
      - Press
      - Bob Fry
      - Issues
      - Bob Fry mailer
      - Jack Diepenbrock
      - SIH - Federated Women's Clubs
      - Tuttle
      - Postage due bills
    - Campaign, 1982 (Box 335-337)
      - S.I. Hayakawa contributors
      - finance, 1982
      - Scheduling
      - Hemming Morse
      - Speech to Republican Convention
      - Political brochures
      - Campaign receipts
      - Campaign letters
      - Campaign expenditures
      - Larry Labovitz correspondence
    - correspondence, 1982 (Box 338-339)
    - Bill and document requests
    - Senior Internship Program
    - SIH thank you letters
    - Hispanic Council
    - Franked mail reports
    - Tam of the Month Awards
    - Staff memos
    - Referrals to D.C.
    - Referrals to S.F.
    - Case work
      - Bruce Case
      - Sherry Gaver
      - Berenda Dutt
      - Ladomato
      - Josette Bonte
      - City of Santa Ana
      - Mono Lake
      - Sally Hashimoto
      - Jacobson Case
      - Ultrasystems Inc.
      - Immigration
    - Special Projects (Box 340-342)
      - U.S. Marshall
        - Southern District California
        - Northern District California
        - Eastern District California
        - Central District California
      - Federal Judges
        - Southern District California
        - Northern District California
        - Eastern District California
        - Central District California
      - U.S. Attorney
        - Southern District California
        - Northern District California
        - Eastern District California
        - Central District California
    - Judiciary Advisory Committee
    - Federal appointments
    - Oceanside
    - Olympics
    - Orange Coast National Park
    - Big Sur
    - D.C. Housing Survey, 1982
    - Beach Erosion Control
    - Seal Beach
    - Project Smile
    - Military Housing
    - Peripheral Canal
    - Laguna Oil Lease
    - Federal Lands Policy
    - Long Beach Airport/Army Reserve
    - Jepson Family Protection Act
    - California expenses, 1980-1981 (Box 343-345)
    - Contributors (Box 346-347)
    - Cassette tapes of SIH speeches
    - Miscellaneous Orange County
    - Orange County Airport
    - Orange County Volunteer letter
    - Upper Newport Bay
    - Orange County Constituency Council
    - Space Shuttle Landing
    - Orange County Urban Park
    - Intern Program
    - Interns and volunteers for Orange County Office
    - General office operations, 1980 (Box 348-350)
      - Office casework
      - Office Managers Reports
      - Scheduling
    - Issues
    - Vacation/Sick leave reports
    - Field Work Reports
    - TV equipment
    - Requests for appointments
    - Resumes
    - California tours
    - Press releases
    - Constituency Council
    - Hispanic Program
    - Minority Program
    - Youth Program
    - Office Management, 1977 (Box 351)
      - Office Managers Report
      - Casework reports
      - Constituent Program
      - Black Constituent Program
      - Youth Program
      - Memos
      - M.T.S.T. Operation
      - Franked mail reports
      - Intern Program
      - Requests for appointments
      - Mail count
      - Plaque from California Young Americans for Freedom
    - Field Reports, 1978 (Box 352-353)
      - Labovitz
      - Notes on office visits
      - Panama Canal
      - Reports to Gene Prat, Adm. Asst.
    - Office Management, 1978 (Box 354-356)
      - Field reports
      - Office Managers Reports
      - Casework reports
      - California tours and press releases
      - Mail counts
      - Office operations
      - Space and office furniture
    - Office Operations, 1979 (Box 357-359)
      - Field work
      - Minority Program
      - Constituency Program
      - Youth Program
      - Hispanic Committee
      - Advisory Committees
      - Casework
      - California tours
      - Office Managers Reports
      - Mobile Office Operations
    - Office Operations, 1979 (Box 360-362)
    - Office Operations, 1982
    - Office Management, 1982 (Box 363)
      - Casework
      - Field work
      - Air Traffic Controllers Strike
      - Advisory Committees
      - Constituency Councils
      - Minority Program
      - Tom Harris
      - Brooks Baldwin Case
      - Accounts
  - San Diego Office (Box 364-388)
  - San Francisco Office (Box 389)
    - Videotapes
    - Video program (Box 390)
    - Christmas card list
    - Constituents Program County files
      - Alameda
      - Contra Costa
      - Fresno
      - Los Angeles/Orange
      - Marin
      - Monterey/Santa Cruz
      - Napa
      - Sacramento
      - San Francisco
      - San Diego
      - San Luis Obispo/Ventura/Santa Barbara
      - San Mateo (Box 391)
      - Santa Clara
      - Sonoma
    - Constituents Program Procedures
    - Constituents Program - general information
    - Rubber stamps for Youth Program
    - Student letters/answers
    - Missing Children Act
    - Disasters in Delta
    - Wilderness Bill
    - Peripheral Canal
    - Refugees
    - Oil leases
    - Handicap issues
    - Washington internships
    - Guest Worker Bill (Box 392)
    - Education
    - FEMA - Lou Polumbo resignation
    - Communications Act
    - Defense issues
    - Budget issues
    - Agriculture issues
    - Three Month Report mailings
    - Black Ministers Program
    - San Francisco Internship Program
    - Mailing list updates
    - January Constituents Council Meeting
    - July Constituents Council Meeting
    - November Constituents Council Meeting
    - Newsletter, May 1981
    - Youth Meeting announcements
    - Youth questionnaire (Box 393)
    - Questionnaire analysis
    - Hayakawa Youth Tour
    - Miscellaneous youth groups
    - Senate Youth Program (Hearst Foundation)
    - Northrop Programs
    - National Youth Advisory Campaign
    - 4-H Youth Program
    - Statehouse Conference on Children and Youth
    - SIH on KABC (tape)
    - Hayakawa Youth Constituents Program, County files (Box 394)
      - Los Angeles
      - Lake
      - Kings
      - Placer
      - Orange
      - Napa
      - Merced
      - Marin
      - Madera
      - Yuba
      - Yolo
      - Tuolomne
      - Tulare
      - Trinity
      - Tehama
      - Stanislaus
      - Sonoma
      - Solano
      - San Francisco
      - San Diego
      - Sacramento
      - San Bernardino
      - Sierra (Box 395)
      - Siskiyou
      - Shasta
      - Santa Cruz
      - Santa Clara
      - Santa Barbara
      - San Mateo
      - San Luis Obispo
      - San Joaquin
    - Youth for Understanding Program (Box 396)
    - Junior Statesman Program
    - Youth questionnaires
    - Change/Add address
    - Scheduling
    - Questionnaire tabulations
    - HYCP sample mailings
    - Sally Campbell (employee lnformation)
    - SIH youth photos
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency
    - Field reports
    - Republican Convention, Monterey (Box 397)
    - Washington Intern information
    - January Constituents Council Meeting
    - December Constituents Council Meeting
    - Aviation (proposed advisory council)
    - SJR 72
    - SJR 72 (State Senate bill)
    - Olive growers labor crisis
    - Manufactured housing issues
    - Delta floods
    - Hayakawa photographs (Box 398-399)
    - Hayakawa awards
    - Intergovernmental Management Training Seminar information
    - Youth information sheets for HYCP
    - HYCP Youth Conference
    - HYCP Youth Opinions on the Draft
    - HYCP Monthly Reports
    - Olympics, 1984
    - HYCP press
    - HYCP weekly column mailing to high schools
    - Hayakawa Youth Tour, 1978
    - Constituent Council Meetings
    - Cattlemen's Association/Livestock Brand Conference
    - Delta Task Force
    - McClellan Air Force Base information
    - Nassan Tandekwire (SIH assistance)
    - Sample youth mailings
    - Sacramento field work
    - Weekly column mailing list
    - Tam of the Month information
    - Taiwan: Trade Mission
    - Volunteers
    - Reports to Phyllis Steiner
    - HYCP questionnaire, revised
    - Recipe: SIH Sukiyaki Caccatore
    - Vietnam: POW/MIAs
    - Projects (Box 400)
      - Peripheral Canal and Group Water
      - Special projects, general information
      - Blue Bird Canyon
      - Media Project - Port Huenema
      - Polynesian Pacific peoples
      - Past projects
      - Polynesian Center (Palos Verdes peninsula Slide South Coast Air Quality Management) (Box 401)
      - Special projects past
      - Federal Workshop
      - All Mission Housing Authority
      - Bar-Bote Fish Ranch
      - Canejo Valley School District
      - Chemehuevi Post Office
      - Forum regulations
      - City of Garden Grove
      - Geronthological Research Project
      - Long Beach Unified School Native American Program
      - City of Long Beach
      - Postal problem
      - 523 West 6th Street, Los Angeles
      - Satellites
      - Synanon (Box 402)
      - Long Beach Weather Station
      - Los Angeles Federal Correctional Center
      - Indian Center of Los Angeles, CETA funding
      - Military Talent Bank
      - Ombe - One stop shops proposal
      - Hilda Sharpless Manor - HUD Project
      - Sports Village
      - United Parcel Service
      - Tahoe bills
      - Tahoe news articles (Box 403)
      - Tahoe Regional Planning Agency
      - Tahoe Sewer Treatment
      - Project Water
      - Youth - Bureau of Indian Affairs
      - Bureau of Indian Affairs - Los Angeles
      - Port Hueneme